<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Find Table</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Detail Text -->
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_default">Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text Default text </string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_1">With 20 years experience, I personally invite you to try us. We use only the freshest local ingredients we can get. All our fish are prepared with care and in-house. You will taste and see what experience makes.</string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_2">Guu with Otokomae in Gastown brings a contemporary twist to the Izakaya. “Otokomae” means “handsome man” or “true man” physically and mentally.\n\nEach dish is carefully crafted to art-like perfection, making them both delicious &amp; visually pleasing. Otokomae is perfect for groups, or for a sophisticated dinner for two at the counter.\n\nWe keep seats for walk-in customers as well. No available seats on opentable does not mean we are fully booked. Please be aware that the time limited per table is two hours during peak hours.</string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_3">Tuc Craft Kitchen is a restaurant and bar in Gastown, Vancouver. Our vision was to create a gathering place that feels like it has always been here. Our food is elegant, rustic, honest … from classic, nostalgic flavours to new inspired dishes. Paired with authentic cocktails, craft beer and a carefully curated wine list, it is dining at our family table.</string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_4">Embracing the harmony of Peruvian and Japanese cultures while incorporating the bounty of the West Coast seafood.</string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_5">The Keg Steakhouse &amp; Bar serves the finest cuts of succulent steak, aged for tenderness and grilled to perfection. Prime rib is a Keg specialty, slow roasted, haamp;nd carved and perfectly seasoned with special Keg spices. The restaurant also serves delicious seafood, memorable appetizers, crisp salads and decadent desserts. A casual ambiance and friendly, very knowledgeable staff are proud and reliable trademarks of The Keg Steakhouse &amp; Bar. You\'ll find a truly comfortable and satisfying dining atmosphere accompanied by a fun and up-scale bar setting where guests can enjoy an excellent wine list, signature Keg martinis, and fresh squeezed juice cocktails.</string>
    <string name="textView_restaurantDetail_6">Celebrating the here and now, Nightingale delivers fresh and vibrant modern Canadian cuisine that’s designed for the way people want to eat today. Fresh vegetables and creative proteins are offered in a range of share plates that contribute to the fun, convivial atmosphere of the industrial-chic space. Located in a heritage building in the heart of downtown Vancouver, Nightingale’s buzzing dining room is anchored by a focal bar that complements the compelling flavour profiles of the food with G&amp;T on tap, an approachable wine list and a range of local craft beers.</string>

    <string name="restaurantName">Restaurant Name</string>
    <string name="menu_bookList">Book List</string>
    <string name="menu_favoriteList">Favorite List</string>

    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>
    <string name="review_default_1">This restaurant is amazing!I should go again.</string>
    <string name="review_default_2">I saw a cockroach in here.I wont go again.</string>
    <string name="review_default_3">This restaurant is amazing!I should go again.</string>

    <string name="book_label">Your Book List</string>
    <string name="fav_label">Your Favorite List</string>
    <string name="index">Find Table</string>
    <string name="icon_contentDescription"/>
    <string name="restaurant_main_visual">Restaurant Main Visual</string>
    <string name="no_data_available">No data</string>
</resources>
